

Sudhir Chahal

3D Graphic Designer

Date of birth:

03.08.1991

Nationality:

Indian

Sex:

Male

Marital Status:

Married

Language:

Hindi / English

Skills

Autodesk MAX •••••

Autodesk Maya ●●●●

AutoCad • • • • •

Photoshop ••••

Coreldraw • • • • • •

Illustrator • • • • • •

Plugin: Vray • • • • • •

Contact: 8287911614

Email : sudhirchahal@gmail.com

Address : Gurugram, Haryana

Portfolio: sudhirchahal.wordpress.com

About

Passionate 3d Designer with more than 7 years of experience in modeling, texturing, lighting, and rendering. Able to quickly synthesize feedback from clients and iterate on work to create the desired final product I am a Quick learner, Adaptive, and Self Motivated person.

Experience

♦ 3D Graphic Designer- Present

Varun Malhotra Designs(June 2019 - Present)

- Responsible for modeling, texturing, lighting, and rendering 3d scenes,
- Interacting with clients for requirements and review calls.
- · Flex, banners, etc.

◆ 3D Artist

Spatial Design Consultants (Aug. 2015 - June 2019)

I was mainly involved in creating 3d visuals for interiors, exteriors, events and exhibitions.

◆ Lighting And Rendering Artist

Extramarks Education Pvt Ltd (June 2014- Aug, 2015

Lighting the final scene(or render) in a style that blends properly with the 3d project. .

Educational Qualification

• M.Sc. - Punjab Technical University

Major - Multimedia

B.Sc. - Kurukshetra University

Major - Multimedia